Horlacher, John Arbitration Records 5587
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- National Broadcasting Co., Inc. vs. Int'l. Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees & Moving Picture Machine Operators of the US & Can., Local 804 (IATSE), 1959-1963 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  Issue: Management rights - job content; rate of pay increase.
- Description National Cylinder Gas Co. Cases, 1959-1967 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  Issue: contract interpretation - holiday pay eligibility, assignment of jobs - remedy for improper assignment.
- National Gypsum Co. vs. USW, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  Issue: call-in-overtime, assignment of jobs - failure to assign.
- National Labor Relations Board, General Counsel vs. National Labor Relations Board Union, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  Issue: promotions - past practice.
- National Sugar Refining Co. vs. Sugar Refinery Workers, Local 1648, 1965-1971 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  Issue: severance pay eligibility; discipline discharge.
- National Sugar Refining Co. vs. Sugar Refinery Workers, Local 1648, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  Issue: reduction in force - crew consist, discipline - suspension.
- National Vulcanized Fibre Co. Cases, 1960-1974 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Philadelphia Naval Shipyard vs. Philadelphia Metal Trades Council, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  Issue: rates of pay -hazard pay.
- NCR Appleton Papers Division, Harrisburg Plant vs. United Paperworkers Int'l. Union, Local 1098, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  Issue: classification of jobs - new job, added duties.
- Neapco Products, Inc. vs. USW, Local 2479, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  Issue: assignment of jobs - discrimination.
- New Jersey Water Co. vs. Int'l. Bro. of Firemen, Oilers, Power House Operators & Maintenance Men, Local 473, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  Issue: posting - refusal to post.
- New System Launderers & Dry Cleaners vs. IBT, Local 676, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  no decision.
- New York & Pennsylvania Co., Inc. vs. United Papermakers & Paperworkers, AFL-CIO, Local 701, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- New York Shipbuilding Corp. vs. IBBISBFH, Local 801, 1954 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- New York Shipbuilding Corp. vs. IBBISBFH, Local 801, 1954-1963 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  Issue: safety; discipline; demotions; assignment of jobs; classification of jobs.
- Newport News Shipbuilding & Dry Dock Co. vs. Peninsula Shipbuilders' Assoc, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Newark School District, Newark, DE vs. Delaware Public Employees, Council 81, AFSCME, Local 218, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  Issue: rates of pay - claim for pay of higher classification.
- Newspaper Publishers Assoc. of Philadelphia vs. Philadelphia Stereotypers Union, Local 7, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  Issue: contract modification - wage adjustment.
- Norristown, Borough of vs. Laborers District Council of Philadelphia and Vicinity, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Northern Metal Co. vs. Industrial Union of Marine & Shipbuilding Workers of America, Local 14, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  Issue: union security - job jurisdiction.
- Nuclear Service & Construction Co., Inc. vs. Amer. Federation of Technical Engineers, Marine Draftsmen's Assoc, Local 209, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  Issue: assignment of jobs - assignment of work outside unit.
- NVF Co. vs. IBPSPMW, Local 770, 1969-1974 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  Issue: discipline discharge, suspension; fringe benefits - Health and Welfare Programs.
- Obringer Home Furniture Co., Div. of Tilmore Corp. vs. IBT, General Warehousemen & Employees, Local 636, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  Issue: rates of pay - increases.
- Olin Mathieson Chemical Corp. Cases, 1961-1967 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  Issue: reduction of force layoff; assignment of jobs overtime
- Orr & Sembover, Inc. vs. USW, 1954-1957 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  Issue: discipline suspension, bumping - seniority; assignment of jobs - assignment of work outside unit.
- Ovens-Corning Fiberglas Corp. Cases, 1960-1971 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Ovens-Corning Fiberglas Corp. Cases, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Ovens-Corning Fiberglas Corp. vs. GBBA, Local 252, 1966-1970 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  Issue: contracting out construction; reduction force assignment of jobs.
- Ovens-Corning Fiberglas Corp. vs. GBBA, Local 252, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 30)
- Ovens-Corning Fiberglas Corp. vs. GBBA, Local 252, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  Issue: past practice-managerial discretion.
- Ovens-Illinois Inc. vs. United Paperworkers Int'l. Union, Local 375, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 32)
- Ovens Yacht Division, Brunswick Corp. vs. Int'l. Union of Marine & Shipbuilding Workers of America, Local 28, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 33)
- Packaging Corp. of America vs. USW, Local 6184, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  Issue: management rights - assignment of jobs.
- Palmer-Shile Co. vs. USW, Local 4193, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  Issue: insubordination - suspension.
- Pangborn Corp. vs. (JAW, Local 842, 1955-1956 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  Issue: discipline - suspension; classification of jobs, classification of jobs - evaluation of job factors.
- Paper Products Mfg. Co. vs. United Papermakers & Paperworkers, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Parade Publications, Inc. vs. Philadelphia Newspaper Printing Pressmen's Union, No. 16, 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  Issue: Management rights -crew size.
- Paragon Oil Co. vs. Truck Drivers & Helpers Union, Local 676, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Paramount Packaging Corp. vs. United Papermakers & Paperworkers of Aroer., Local 35, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Paramount Paper Products Co. vs. United Paperworkers of America, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Paterson Parchment Paper Co. vs. Int'l. Bro. of Papermakers, Local 500, 1956-1965 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  Issue: management rights - determination of existence of vacancy, overtime - assignment of jobs
- Pathmark Supermarkets, Preakness store vs. Retail Store Employees Union, Local 1262, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Peerless Steel Equipment Co. vs. USW, Local 1619, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Penn Central Co. vs. William 0. Volkmer, Claimant, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  Issue: severance pay - voluntary quit.
- Penco Metal Products Division, Alan Wood Steel Co. vs. Int'l. Assoc. of Bridge, Structural & Ornamental Iron Workers, Shopmen's Local No. 502, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Penn Dispatch, Inc. vs. IBT, Local 773, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  Issue: holidays & holiday pay, layoff - notice.
- Penn Fruit Co., Inc. vs. Produce, Poultry, Fish, Oystermen, Drivers & Helpers, Local 929, 1966-1971 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  Issue: discipline discharge; vacations - eligibility.
- Penn Packing Co. vs. Amalgamated. Heat Cutters & Butcher Workmen, Local 195, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Penn Ventilator Co., Inc. vs. United Electrical Radio & Machine Workers of America (UE), Local 179, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  Issue: posting - vacancies.
- Pennland Printing Co. vs. Philadelphia Typographical Union, No. 2, 1967-1971 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  Issue: rates of pay increases, shutdown - assignment of jobs, transfers - management rights, contract interpretation, jurisdiction - crossing craft lines, discipline - discharge.
- Pennsylvania, Commonwealth of vs. American Federation of State, County & Municipal Employees, Council 13 (AFSCME), 1974-1976 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Pennsylvania, Commonwealth of Dept. of Environmental Resources - Bureau of Forestry, District 1 vs. AFSCME, maintenance & trades unit, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  Issue: layoff - failure to recall.
- Pennsylvania, Commonwealth of, Liquor Control Board vs. Retail Clerks Union, PA State Organizing Committee, 1971-1975 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  Issue: interest arbitration, discipline discharge, assignment of jobs - past practice.
- Pennsylvania, Commonwealth of, Probation & Parole, Board of vs. AFSCME, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Pennsylvania, Commonwealth of, Property & Supplies, Dept. of vs. AFSCME - clerical, administrative L fiscal unit, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  Issue: probationary employees - termination of employment.
- Pennsylvania, Commonwealth of, Warrendale Youth Development Center vs. Pennsylvania Social Services Union, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Pennsylvania. Commonwealth of, Transportation, Dept. of vs. AFSCME, clerical, administrative & fiscal unit, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  Issue: rates of pay - premium pay.
- Pennsylvania, Commonwealth of, Turnpike Commission vs. IBT, Local 77, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Pennsylvania Electric Co. Cases, 1964-1969 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  Issue: supervisor & foremen - bargaining work - performance of, discipline - discharge.
- Pennsylvania Forge Co. vs. IAN, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  Issue: reduction in workforce - layoff.
- Pennsylvania Malleable Iron Corp. vs. Int'l. Holders & Allied Workers Union, Local 287, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  Issue: rates of pay - piecework vs. day work
- Pennsylvania Pump & Compressor Co. vs. UE, Local 141, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  Issue: fringe benefits - bonuses.
- Pequannock Foodtown Supermarket vs. Retail Store Employees Union, Local 1262, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  Issue: termination of employment - discharge vs. layoff.
- Perfect Foods, Inc. Amer. Bakery & Confectionery Workers Int'l. Union, Local 492, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  Issue: vacancies - posting.
- Perkasie Industries Corp. vs. IBEW, Local 1841, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Peters Township, Pennsylvania vs. Peters Township Police, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  Issue: rates of pay; fringe benefits.
- Philadelphia, City of vs. Fraternal Order of Police, Philadelphia Lodge, #5, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  Issue: rates of pay; overtime.
- Philadelphia, School District of, 1971-1972 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  Issue: layoff temporary, transfers discrimination, transfers - seniority.
- Philadelphia Coke Division, Eastern Gas & Fuel Associates vs. UMW, District 50, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Philadelphia Dairy Products Co., Inc. vs. Food Driver Salesmen, Dairy & Ice Cream Workers, Local 463, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  Issue: discipline - suspensions, discharge.
- Philadelphia Gear Works, Inc. vs. IAM, District Lodge #1; vs. Gear Workers Lodge #864 Dist. #1, 1958-1972 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  Issue: discipline - layoff as discipline; strikes slowdowns & stoppages; discipline - discharge.
- Philadelphia Gear Works, Inc. vs. IAM, District Lodge #1; vs. Gear Workers Lodge #864 Dist. #1, 1958-1972 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Philadelphia Inquirer vs. IAM, District Lodge #1; vs. Philadelphia Mailers Union No 14; vs. Philadelphia Typographical Union No 2., 1950-1972 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  Issue: discipline discharge; contracts side agreements; reinstatement - refusal.
- Philadelphia Inquirer vs. IAM, District Lodge #1; vs. Philadelphia Mailers Union No 14; vs. Philadelphia Typographical Union No 2., 1950-1972 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Philadelphia Inquirer vs. IAM, District Lodge #1; vs. Philadelphia Mailers Union No 14; vs. Philadelphia Typographical Union No 2., 1950-1972 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Philadelphia Inquirer vs. IAM, District Lodge #1; vs. Philadelphia Mailers Union No 14; vs. Philadelphia Typographical Union No 2., 1950-1972 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Philadelphia Newspaper, Inc. and Philadelphia Newspaper & Magazine Chauffeurs and Handlers, Local No. 628, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  Issue: bargaining unit work (includes briefs, draft, notes, exhibit).
- Philadelphia Newspaper, Inc. vs. Philadelphia Typographical Union, No. 21967 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Philadelphia Payment Center of Social Security Administration vs. American Federation of Government Employees, Local 2006, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 2a)
  Issue: union election - no determination.
- Philadelphia Rust Proof Co. and Metal Polishers, Buffers, Platers & Helpers Int'l. Union, Local 90, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  Issue: reinstatement after sick leave.
- Philadelphia State Hospital vs. AFSCME, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  Issue: holidays & holiday pay - leave of absence (includes exhibits, notes, briefs)
- Philadelphia Suburban Transportation Co. and Transport Workers' Union (TWU) Local No. 267., 1954 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  Issue: rates of pay - increase.
- Philadelphia Suburban Transportation Co. and Transport Workers' Union (TWU) Local No. 234., 1954 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  Issue: rates of pay red circle rates.
- Philadelphia Suburban Transportation Co. and Transport Workers' Union (TWU) Local No. 234., 1954 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  Issue: discharge - insubordination.
- Philadelphia Suburban Transportation Co. and Transport Workers' Union (TWU) Local No. 234., 1955 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Philadelphia Suburban Transportation Co. and Transport Workers' Union (TWU) Local No. 234., 1955 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Philadelphia Suburban Transportation Co. and Transport Workers' Union (TWU) Local No. 234., 1955 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  Issue: assignment of jobs - change in procedure.
- Philadelphia Suburban Transportation Co. and Transport Workers' Union (TWU) Local No. 234., 1957 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  Issue: discipline - working conditions - accident.
- Philadelphia Wholesale Distributors, Inc. and Teamsters Local 513, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  Issue: discharge -theft - unauthorized taking of property (includes notes & draft).
- Philadelphia Zoological Garden and AFSCME, Local 752, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  Issue: quit - reinstatement following.
- Philanthropic Mutual Life Insurance Co. vs. Insurance Agents Int'l. Union, AFL-CIO, Local 5, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  Issue: defraud.
- Philco Corp. vs. IUERMW, Local 101, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  Arbitrability - wage rates.
- Philco Corp. vs. IUERMW, Local 102, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  Issue: transfer - bargaining unit work - rates of pay.
- Philco Corp. vs. IUERMW, Local 101, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  Issue: lay off - bumping - ability vs. seniority.
- Philco Corp. vs. IUERMW, Local 102, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  Issue: discipline -suspension - union activity, overtime.
- Philco Corp. vs. IUERMW, Local 102, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  Issue: layoff - inter-departmental bumping - seniority.
- Philco Corp. vs. IUERMW, Local 102, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Philco Corp. vs. IUERMW, Local 101, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  Issue: layoff-temporary - failure to observe seniority.
- Philco Corp. vs. IUERMW, Local 101, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  Issue: refusal of overtime.
- Philco Corp. vs. IUERMW, Local 101, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  Issue: classification of jobs - change in work assignments.
- Philco Corp. vs. IUERMW, Local 101, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  Issue: absences - reporting.
- Philco-Ford Corp. vs. (JAW, Local 1695, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  Issue: absence - proof of illness (includes exhibits, notes, draft & transcript)
- Philco-Ford Corp. vs. IUERMW, Local 102, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  Issue: layoff -seniority (includes draft, transcript, exhibits, notes).
- Phoenixville Area School District vs. Phoenixville Area Education Assn, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Phoenixville, the Borough of, vs. Police Dept. of the Borough of Phoenixville, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  Issue: interest - rates of pay (includes transcript, notes, exhibits).
- Phototype Engraving Co. vs. Philadelphia Lithographers & Photoengravers Int'l. Union, Local 7-P, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  Issue: layoff - overtime during (includes draft, notes, exhibits).
- Pittsburgh Plate Glass Co. and Glass Bottle Blowers Assn. of U.S. & Canada, Local 32, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  Issue: layoff - failure to recall discrimination, rates of pay, motion to reopen hearing (of case #1).
- Pittsburgh Plate Glass Co. vs. Glass & Ceramic Workers. of N. American (UGCW), Local 112, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  Issue: subcontracting.
- Pittsburgh Plate Glass Co. vs. Int'l. Chemical Workers Union, Local 45, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  Issue: discharge - theft.
- Pittsburgh Plate Glass Co. vs. Window Glass Cutters League of America, AFL-CIO, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  Issue: bargaining unit work.
- Pittsburgh Plate Glass Co. vs. OCAW, Local 8-2340, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  Issue: discipline - negligence.
- Pittsburgh Plate Glass Co. vs. UGCW, Local 112, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  Issue: pre-shift overtime - premium pay.
- Pickard Industries Corp. vs. Industrial Workers' Union, Local 837, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  Issue: discharges -absence & absenteeism.
- PPG Industries, Inc. vs. Int'l. Union of District 50, UMW, Local 12978, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  Issue: discharge -offensive language and past record.
- Poloron Products of Pa., Inc. vs. Lodge 868 of District No. 128, IAM, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  Issue: incentive pay - equal distribution.
- Pottstown Memorial Medical Center vs. 1199, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  Issue: vacation - computation, continuous service (includes draft, exhibits, notes).
- Pottstown Mercury, Peerless Publications, Inc. vs. Pottstown Typographical Union 715, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  Issue: fringe benefits - pension plan.
- Porter, H.K., Inc. Cases, 1960-1967 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  Issue: reduction in force - work distribution, discipline discharge, seniority computation, layoff- notice.
- Precision Drawn Steel Co. vs. Int'l. Assoc. of Bridge, Structural & Ornamental Iron Workers, Shopmen's Local 502, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  Issue: termination of employment - inability.
- Precision Drawn Steel Co. vs. USW, Local 6177, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  Issue: discipline - discharge
- Progress Mfg. Co. vs. Amal. Lithographers of Amer., Local 11, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  Issue: severance pay -management's obligation to pay; arbitration procedure: appeal & review of award.
- Progressive Furniture Co. vs. Upholsters' Int'l. Union, Furniture & Allied Workers, Local 37, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  Issue: time studies - incentive pay & incentive systems.
- Progressive Supermarkets, Inc. vs. Amalgamated Food & Allied Workers Union, Local 56, 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  Issue: discipline discharge, layoff - seniority.
- Publicker Industries, Inc. vs. Distillery Workers, Local 263, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 47)
  Issue: workweek - shift schedule change, classification of jobs -discontinuance of classification and/or job; classification of jobs - bargaining units; assignment of jobs - remedy for improper assignment.
- Pure Carbon Co. vs. IUE, Local 502, 1956 (Box 14, Folder 48)
  Issue: discipline - refusal of overtime.
- Purex Corp. vs. OCAW, Local 8-398, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 49)
- Purolator Products Co. vs. UAW, Local 895, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 50)
  Issue: assignment of jobs - assignment of work outside union.
- Quaker City Bus Co. vs. Amalgamated. Assoc. of Street, Electric Railway & Motor Coach Employees of Amer., Division 1112, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  Issue: holidays & holiday pay; rates of pay, retroactive pay.
- Quaker Oats Co. vs. Int'l. Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink & Distillery Workers of Amer., Local 221, 1958-1968 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  Issue: assignment of jobs.
- RCA Victor Division of Radio Corp. of America vs. UE, Local 103, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  Issue: rates of pay -retroactive pay, layoff - reduction in force.
- Rack Rite Distributors, Inc. vs. IBT, Local 776, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  Issue: classification of jobs - rates of pay
- Radio Corp. of America, vs. IUE, Local 110, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Reading, Pennsylvania, City of vs. Policemen of the City of Reading, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  Issue: rates of pay -increases.
- Reading Eagle Co. vs. Reading Typographical Union #86, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Refractory and Insulation Corp. vs. USW, Local 5341, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Regal Corrugated Box Co. vs. IBPSPHW, Local 375, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Reinforcing Steel Contractors Assoc. vs. Int'l. Assoc. of Iron Workers, Local 405, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  Issue: vacation pay - computation.
- Roberts Volkswagen, Inc. vs. IBT, Local 676, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  Issue: rates of pay - commissions.
- Robertson Mfg. Co. vs. UGCW, Local 76, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Roco Manser Precision Engineering Corp. vs. USW, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  Issue: layoff-failure to recall; layoff -insurance eligibility.
- Rockwell Corp., North America (TMW Division) vs. USW, Local 6996, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  Issue: plant rules - coffee breaks & rest periods.
- Roebling's Sons, John A. (division of Colorado Fuel & Iron Corp.) vs. USW Locals, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  Issue: assignment of jobs, layoff, rates of pay - incentive pay; assignment of jobs - seniority.
- Rohm & Haas Co. vs. UGCW, 1956-1973 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  Issue: discipline - discharge; discipline suspension, classification of jobs - rates of pay; classification of jobs - new jobs, plant rules - coffee breaks & rest periods.
- Roller-Smith Corp. vs. USW, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  Issue: discipline - discharge; layoff - seniority.
- Roma, F. Brothers Barber Shops vs. Barbers Union, Local #9, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Royal Pioneer Paper Box Mfg. Co. vs. IBPSPMW, Local 286, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Royster, F.S. Guano Co. vs. UMW, District 50, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  Issue: assignment of jobs - past practice.
- SKF Industries, Inc. vs. USW, Local 2898, 1948-1951 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  Issue: arbitrability - classification of jobs, classification of jobs - evaluation of job factors.
- Scott Paper Co. vs. IBPSPMW, 1966-1971 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  Issue: overtime computation, vacations - schedules.
- Scranton-Spring Brook Water Service Co. vs. Federal Labor Union #18047, The Meter Workers Union, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  Issue: rates of pay - increases; overtime -computation.
- Sea Gull Lighting Products, Inc. vs. UE, Local 163, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Sea-Land Service, Inc. vs. OPEIU, Local 155, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  Issue: funeral leave & funeral pay.
- Segal Typesetting Co. vs. Philadelphia Typographical Union #2, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  Issue: management rights -rates of pay.
- Seip, Walter L. Inc. vs. IBT, Local 773, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 27)
- Selas Corp. of Amer. vs. UAW, Local 585, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 28)
- Serta Mattress Co. vs. Upholsterers Int'l. Union, Local 404, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 29)
- Sexton, John & Co. IBT, Local 470, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 30)
- Sharp Corp. vs. Lithographers & Photoengravers Int'l. Union, Local 14L, 1967-1969 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  Issue: discipline suspension, rates of pay; rates of pay -premium pay; rates of pay - increases; holiday pay.
- Sharpies Co., Division of Penn Salt Chemical Corp. vs. IUE, Local 115, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  Issue: discipline -warnings.
- Shop Rite Supermarkets, Consolidated Supermarkets Inc., vs. Retail Store Employees Union, Local 1262, 1964-1970 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  Issue: classification of jobs - rates of pay, Issue: discipline - discharge.
- Sickel's Shop Rite Super Market vs. Retail Clerks Int'l. Union, Local 1360, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 34)
- Sim-Kar Lighting Fixture Co. vs. IBEW, Local 1841, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 35)
- Simonds Abrasive Co. vs. UAW, Local 293, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 36)
- Sinclair Refining Co. vs. OCAW, Local 12-234; Highway Truck Drivers & Helpers, Local 107, 1955-1963 (Box 15, Folder 37)
- Slap Buick Inc. vs. Buick Dealers Employees Assoc, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 38)
- Sley System Garages vs. Transport Workers Union of Amer., Local 700, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 39)
- Snyder Mfg. Co. vs. Metal Polishers, Buffers, Platers & Helpers International Union, Local 90, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 40)
- Sohio Pipe Line Co. vs. OCAW, Local 8-234, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  Issue: assignment of jobs - temporary assignment.
- Sorensen Industries, Inc. vs. USW, 1957-1971 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  Issue: layoff seniority, discipline - discharge.
- South Jersey Gas Co. vs. Federal Labor Union #24893, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  Issue: assignment of jobs - remedy for improper assignment.
- Spartan Chrome Furniture Mfg. Co. vs. IAM, District Lodge #1, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  Issue: vacations - continuous service.
- Sperry Rand Corp. Cases, 1968-1970 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  Issue: management rights - assignment of jobs, assignment of jobs - seniority.
- Sprague & Henwood, Inc. vs. IAM, Lodge 1971, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 46)
- Stackpole Carbon Co. vs. IUE, Local 502, 1956 (Box 15, Folder 47)